BGM
Here we go, Apkami, and this time we have Nanami Kubota from Ocha-no-Oma and Natsumi Nakayama from Ocha-no-Oma.
This time we have Nanami Kubota from Ocha no Oma and Natsumi Nakayama from Ocha no Oma.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
So let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at two of our MCs.
I, Nanami Kubota, am currently on a 47 prefecture tour for Ocha-no-Oma.
I'm Nanami Kubota, and I'd like to talk about it.
Recently, I've been into something.
That's right, that's right.
Self-introductions by MCs
Normally, I would say
I'll do my best again today! I'm Nanami Kubota! but lately I've been trying to make a gag or something.
I mean, it's really just something silly, but I've been doing something a little different, like box-stepping.
It doesn't stop!
We're all a little bored, so we're trying to see if we can make everyone who watches the show laugh.
But I guess it's the first day of the show...
But as the days went by, our ideas became fewer and fewer, and it became more and more difficult to decide whether to accept or not to accept the show.
But as the days went by, we started to draw less and less, and it became more and more a case of either you get it or you don't. We haven't been able to produce very good works lately, so we're going to try to draw more and more.
Kubo and Nanami are always thinking about the members, which helps me a lot.
I, Nakayama, am trying to reduce the amount of luggage we have to carry during rehearsals and tours.
I'm trying to reduce the amount of luggage I have to carry during rehearsals and tours.
Rehearsal goods are quite bulky, and I feel that they are one of the reasons why we have a lot of luggage.
But by using shoes made of a single piece of cloth, like ballet shoes, for example, you can reduce the amount of luggage, so it's not just me.
Recently, not only me but also Kubo and Nanami often use thin shoes like ballet shoes for rehearsals.
In my opinion, it's a great way to reduce the amount of baggage.
The actual shoes are usually very thin, like ballet shoes, and they are very comfortable to wear.
I'm sure you'll be happy to know that I'm not the only one who's had the pleasure of working with you on this project.
I'm going to start with the making of the music video for JuiceJuice's "Love What You Don't Have".
Here is the making of the music video for JuiceJuice's newest single "Naimono Love" which will be released on May 15!
Here is the making of the music video for JuiceJuice's newest single, "Love What Is Not," which will be released on May 15.
Here is the making of the music video for JuiceJuice's newest single, "What's not there", which will be released on May 15.
Music
Good morning.
I'm Sakura Ishiyama.
My name is Sakura Ishiyama.
Today, my makeup looks pretty strong.
It's as sparkly as the costume,
My eyelashes are so right.
It's true.
My eyelashes look really good,
The bangs are unusually thin.
We have the same sequins.
We are sequin friends.
Yay.
I'll do my best with glitter.
Yes, I will.
bano coai
i О
goo
I'm not bokkari with elik something.
flap flap flap
That's why
Die-die-die.
I know what you're talking about.
It's not that easy.
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Soli mera lee, don't dream
Love Love Love
Give me your love
me I'll become a forest where I'll know what's going on
The same feeling
me
Me
Though lines are no longer enough
That you don't sing
It's not a selfish feeling
You're gonna make me love you
Yes, the future is unwavering
Love, love, love, love
I'll give you a voice
Don't waver Love Love Love
You are Your Love
The booth is Jayne with a boo-boo...
There it is... how do you like it... the costumes are in the colors of the members and each has its own shape.
I'm looking forward to seeing the dancers in their costumes and the stocking stuffers!
The studio is colorful and shiny, so please look at the colors clearly.
Yes, so let the yawning begin!
Bjorn!
I'm hoping that the "BYOON" and "D-melody" will be a bit like "E-music", and that the sound will be more like "E-music".
Yes, so, start yawning!
I hope that the "BYOON" and "D-melody" will be a bit like "E-music" and that Erihari will change the channel.
You know...,
I think I'm dealing with a strong woman who is not so strong, but I'm also a strong woman who says, "I won't be a part of this forever, I might fly away to someone else, so I have to do my best,
I think these three girls are the image of that kind of strong woman, and I think I did my best to show that today.
I think the gap is important.
Gaps are important.
I hope to show various gaps in this music video.
It was fun.
We are professionals who can bring out the cute and the cool in one line.
We are professionals.
Are we professionals?
It's okay if you want to cut out something rash.
It's okay if the younger members are UIC.
It's okay, it's okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five.
Shine boy I know myself but
I'm so excited, I'm so excited, I'm so excited
You're such a liar, give it to me.
Surprise, surprise, surprise.
I'm getting my hopes up a little bit.
You don't even notice the new nails or the new hairdo.
You're used to compliments. You think I'm cute.
Maybe it's time for a little upscale, good-smelling love.
Surprise, surprise. Love with an uplifting fragrance might be nice.
I'm not sure I can resist someone a little more exciting.
A ring of a different color
Matching barkers.
I'm actually really into you.
I don't have one, because I'm Lewis, you know.
So, you know, vague lines just don't cut it anymore.
I know I can't measure up. It's not easy.
I want your love, love, love, love
So real my love you and me
Love love love love Now you give me your love
You and me, what I don't have love love love
Give me more your love
We just finished shooting the music video for "Nai mono love"!
I think it's getting warmer now.
It was still a little bit cold when we shot the dance scene.
We shot a lot of different lip and image scenes for each of them.
What was the most memorable moment for you?
This time, we shot a lot of image scenes and solo lip shots.
I think we shot a lot of dance scenes as the main subject.
The cameraman did a great job.
The cameraman worked really hard and took a lot of pictures from various angles and with a lot of movement.
I'm sure the images will be full of realism.
I can't wait to see it.
This time, everyone's costumes are in the members' colors.
That's right, the members' colors!
They all match each other's color.
They all have their own unique costumes.
I hope you will pay attention to them.
I think you will be able to see their smiling faces and the gaps between their cool and cool sides.
I think you'll see a lot of smiling faces and cool gaps between the members.
Please watch the music video!
Bye bye!
Thank you very much!
Yes, I watched the making of JuiceJuice's music video for "Troubled Love".
I thought that JuiceJuice was really good at making sexy and mature expressions.
I can't really do this kind of hand gesture with tea.
I can't really do this kind of thing with tea, but you can make sexy hand gestures.
I was really impressed by how well everyone did it.
I was really impressed by the solo lip scene.
I was really impressed by the solo lip scene, but in my case, I still have to work on the parts other than the one I sing.
I don't know how to say it, but...
I don't know how to say it, but I'm not sure if I'm ready for free dancing.
I haven't really settled on my part yet, but JuiceJuice, you guys are all so into your own worldviews.
I learned a lot from the way they filmed the solo lip scene.
This is the making of Juice Juice's music video for "Miaemono Love".
Juice Juice News Single
Naimono Love
Now on sale
Cheer up!
Next is here!
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 making video
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30th and 31st.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024
We'll be focusing on the solos and shuffle units.
Please have a look!
Boo-boo!
We'll do our best.
Hope you enjoyed the show.
It hasn't started.
But when I'm looking at this, I feel like it's already over.
Yeah, it is.
Good job, self.
I'm sorry. Life is what it is.
I'm an adventure
School School School School School School School
School, School, School, School, School, School, School, School, School, School, School, School
I think everyone is trying a little harder.
Saito and Nishizaki need to work a little harder
I want to sing a little more to the front
There are so many solos in this song.
There are a lot of solos where you can sing by yourself.
I would like to see a little more energy there, too.
I don't want it to sound like I'm just going in and singing softly.
So please decide how you want to sing.
Yes, sir.
I'm Sigiri...
Last year we drew lots for the first time.
We all failed.
Oh, really?
Ten of us didn't win.
We all said it was really frustrating.
So this time, five of us tried.
That's not half.
These three of them are here on this team.
I'm very happy.
Sachiko, go ahead.
I'm Kudo, and it's been a few years since I've won a lottery like this.
I've wanted to win for a long time.
And it's the first time for five of us to play two games.
I was hoping to cover a song by a large group anyway.
I was so happy to be able to do it!
From now on...
I guess so.
What do you think?
Well... this was Saito's first time winning the Hina Fest lottery.
I've admired Hello Project since before I became a trainee.
I'm glad I won this time.
I was so happy.
So I hope we can make the best performance together.
That's right.
As you can see, I, Risasaki, was really nervous from the rehearsal.
As you can see, I understand.
But to be able to sing the songs of our seniors on a big stage like this is a really precious experience for us.
I'm really looking forward to the performance as much as I can.
I'm looking forward to it.
I was probably the last one to play after everyone else had left, right?
That's why I knew they were good singers the moment I saw them.
That's right.
So this song is not for the five of us to sing together, that's for sure.
So I'm pretty much looking forward to it.
I'm sure you all know how it was going to be.
But I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best
The shuffle is coming up soon
Oh, what a surprise!
I'm excited!
Fun!
Next time, I'm a little breathless, almost frantic.
I'm kind of nervous, but I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll do my best to make it exciting and exciting!
I learned this reverse song first when I found out that Hirabetsu was going to start,
I'm very nervous, but I'm also feeling the most shizukake in my body,
I'm also very happy to know that I'm going to have a shibikake with Hanashi-chan.
Oh, no!
I'm going to sing "To the corner.
I made a mistake rehearsing. I'm really sorry.
It's "Kakaku".
Corner corner.
I'm pretty nervous! And I was thinking of doing it with my head, like, "Let's hear your voice.
I've never said that before in rehearsal.
I'm nervous. I'm nervous.
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
This is not good.
My heart is overflowing.
I'm not going to live my life fooling around
No, no, no, no
No.
I'm adrenaline
Sukisuki, sukisuki, sukisuki
I tension
Let's hear it out!
Sanse Sanmen
Heart, Adrenality
If I crystallize this, it'll stay like this
I'm adrenable
Kiki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-ki-free
My goal
I took a chance.
We had fun!
Already, one song and we are sweating.
We finished at 9:00 and I knew it was just a song, so it was very energetic,
It was my first time to perform at this show,
I've never been to this show before, but I'm already excited until the end of the show. It was just one song.
It was good.
It's over.
I have no more regrets!
I've done it.
I had been so nervous until now,
I think I was able to enjoy the performance.
I think I could have done more, but
I think I could have done more, but I want to make the most of this experience from now on.
It was a lot of fun.
Well then, sera is over!
I think this concert is already over.
This premium concert
I was the most nervous and I think I was the most vocal.
I don't know what to say.
The song is really an adrenaline no-no,
Tsubaki-san performs it with a large group,
I thought it would be a little less powerful with 5 members.
So, I thought, "How can we make it work with just five people?
We talked about how we could make it work.
So we talked about how we could make it work.
I think everyone did their best.
Yes, I think it turned out to be a good show.
And at the beginning of the song
I put in a voice like "voice of voice" at the beginning of the song.
So the audience got really excited.
The audience got excited.
They were really excited.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
You were so cool!
You were so cool.
About Miku Nishizaki...
Miku Nishizaki was very nervous during the rehearsals.
Even before the show, she was so nervous that she didn't know what to do.
But now that I've seen the video of the performance, I can see that she didn't seem so nervous.
Miku's performance didn't make me feel that nervousness.
Miku's performance was pretty high.
There was a solo part with a high pitch sound, but even in that part, I was really impressed by the gutsy performance that didn't make me feel nervous at all.
I was really impressed by her performance and I felt that she is indeed Miku Suzaki.
I heard that everyone was surprised when they saw the announcement.
But I also saw how they were enjoying their performance, so I was really impressed by the power of the five of them.
I was really impressed by how the five of us were able to bring that kind of intensity to the stage.
That's all for Hello Project Hina Fest 2024!
This is the making of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024.
Let's take it easy today!
Tea ceremony horse Natsume Nakayama
Apkami by Natsume Nakayama from Ocha no Ma
Next up is here!
Tsubaki Factory Power Flower Now is the Time to Become One Eye Vocal Recording
Tsubaki Factory's latest album "Power Flower: Now is the Time to be an Eye".
Mao Akiyama's vocal recording session.
She's really hyped up!
Okay, did you touch it?
That's a lot of pressure, isn't it?
But I've been wanting to try my hand at rapping lately.
I see.
I'm so happy.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
Well, let's start with the first act, "Amel".
The signal for the beginning, the third act.
Modest sledding, but still ice
Red blooms the fighting spirit, firm and unmovable
The vividness of the music is striking.
Zen
If I were to go with a slightly thicker, lower center of gravity feel...
Also, the verb "fighting spirit" and the verb "to fight" are in the middle of the sentence.
Make the "fighting spirit" a little clearer.
If it's too short, it becomes "zhi".
So I'll make it "fighting spirit.
The curtain rises, signaling the beginning of the show.
A modest sled, but with a hidden chastisement.
A child in red, a child with no hard feelings
The brightness that catches the eye
Youth
I'll take this now.
Okay, I'll continue.
Then I'll continue.
Firm and unmoving hearts, with eye-catching vividness
All together Advanced religion
Everything gonna be alright
A little tighter.
All together, advanced religion, unreachable by all
I'm going to go with a pretty sharp edge.
Everything gonna be alright
Okay, okay.
Then the other side
Firm and immobile
the most eye-catching
to the vividness
Gather round, all of you
Now we're talking.
Spiritualism
If you know what I'm talking about, then jump on that face and make a fuss with both hands.
Jiggle, jiggle, jiggle, bye-bye, bye-bye, showtime
no one has ever done it before
Here I come
Everything gonna be alright
camellia, hanami, everything on the ground
Oh yeah, that's the feeling
Keep the rhythm a little bit
And, uh, try to keep it a little lower and thicker
Um...
Like a rapper.
Okay, one more time.
Hard and unmoving
It's so striking
To the vividness
Everyone gather together
Now that's a deal.
Spiritualism
If you know what I'm talking about, then jump on that face and make a fuss with both hands.
Jiggle, jiggle, jiggle, bye-bye, bye-bye, showtime
no one has ever done it before
Here I come
Everything gonna be alright
camellia, hanami, everything on the ground
Yes, yes, yes
We're just getting started.
Let's just get a shot of it.
Okay, that's cool. Let's try the next one.
Let's make it a little more "e" sound.
I'll pull it out so it'll be a little "hee"...
Graceful. Graceful.
Be careful there.
Let's do it again.
Let's try it again.
Empress Ting, Ghana, Bee-O-Line, Svakin, Floral Path, Bath, Insta-In, Gassa-In, everything's fine.
The overlapping forces are heading towards the blue sky, which is dignified, graceful, and beautiful all over the world.
Okay, let's go next.
Okay, I'll go next.
I want to make the whole world bloom with dignity, grace, and beauty.
Red, red, redder, redder, your words keep shining
Yes, that way.
Yes.
Plus.
Uh, accent.
A little more rhythm.
Yes.
I want the whole world to bloom I can't make this dream come true on my own
I want you to keep shining redder and redder
Aaaaah!
Kotowa!
Kotto waa!
Yeah, there's no point in singing that high up.
I'm glad I don't sing downstairs.
It's like, "Oh, thank goodness I don't sing downstairs.
Yes.
Yeah, it's good.
Next is the second half of the chorus.
Yes.
From this part, it starts to sound a bit like a rap song.
Power flower, I could get a little tighter rhythm.
Ah, power flower, power flower, power flower!
Oh, yes.
Pan-pan, pan-pan.
And...,
Pan-pan, pan-pan, and move forward with the same feeling.
To a place I've never seen before.
Power, Flower.
Yes, be careful where you frame that flower.
Yes, pan-pan.
Yes, sir. One more time, then.
Please.
Keep shining redder and redder on you.
Now is the time to become one eye, to join our feelings together and move forward.
To a place you've never seen before.
Power, flower, now is the time to be one eye.
Go forward with all your heart.
To a place you've never seen before.
Power, Flower.
The last flower is about to rush in.
Let's just take the last flower.
Please do.
Power, Flower.
Now is the time to become one eye.
Let's move forward with all our hearts.
To a place you've never seen before.
Power, Flower.
Is that what I think it is?
That's what I mean.
Yes, that's it. So that's all.
Yes.
Okay, then.
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
That was great, wasn't it? It was great. I don't know how to say it, but the rhythm of rap music is very difficult.
There are many rap songs in Ochadama, but the rhythm is very difficult, and it is quite a task just to memorize it,
I thought it was really cool how you made the rap music your own, or how you accentuated it.
I was really impressed by your ability to immediately absorb, understand, and act on what the director said,
I was really impressed by his ability to respond to the director. I was very impressed by his ability to respond to the situation. I would like to do my best to understand what he said immediately.
Tsubaki Factory, Power Flower, now is the time to unite! It was a vocal recording by Mao Akiyama.
No matter how ragged you are.
High to Diamond
A New Night
More This Star
Beyond High To Diamond May 29 On Sail
Don't worry, we'll manage
It's time for Nanami Kubota and Natsume Nakayama to say goodbye to Apkami!
Well, we've seen a lot of videos this time.
I, Nakayama, was impressed by the making of JuiceJuice's "Naimono Love" music video.
I still feel that I'm not very good at making sad or cool expressions in the solo lip scene.
I learned a lot from it.
I also learned a lot from the smooth movement of the upper body only, which I can refer to in the future.
Yes, I, Kubota, was impressed by the adrenaline-dame of Hinafes 2024.
I was really impressed with the adrenaline medicine of HinaFest 2024, but I have to remember a lot of things at HinaFest.
It's a lot of things to remember at HinaFest.
But everyone was so cool that they didn't show it.
I don't think we had such a long rehearsal period.
It was really cool how the five of us created a stage together.
I hope we will win the lottery next year, too.
I hope we will win the lottery next year, and I will do my best.
In this issue of APKAMI, we're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UPFRONT GROUP.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time, our partners Nanami Kubota from Ocha no Oma and Natsumi Nakayama from Ocha no Oma.
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami: Making of JuiceJuice Aiko Music Video Shooting and
We will be showing the behind-the-scenes of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024!
Thank you for watching!